http://www.eldoradochemical.com/privacy_policy

Skip to main content
Customize Search
Main menu
HomeCOVID-19 UpdateAbout LSBWho is LSB?RecognitionLSB Values StatementLSB Ethics HotlineContact UsCareersProduct MarketsAgrochemical BusinessIndustrial ChemicalsMining ProductsFacilitiesCherokee Nitrogen LLCEl Dorado Chemical CompanyEl Dorado Nitrogen LLCPryor Chemical CompanyEl Dorado Agricultural ProductsProductsChemicalSafety Data SheetsCherokee Nitrogen LLCEl Dorado Chemical CompanyEl Dorado Nitrogen LLCPryor Chemical CompanyInvestors
Home » Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
This document was last updated October 31, 2012
LSB Industries, Inc. (“LSB”) is sensitive to privacy issues on the internet. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat information we receive about you on our website.
Collection of Information
In general, you can visit the LSB website without telling us who you are or revealing personal information. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the email addresses of visitors. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used to measure site usage and to improve the content of our site.
LSB also collects information about which pages users visit within the LSB website. This site visitation data is not linked with personal information.
Use of Information
The general information we collect is used to enhance visitor experience at the site, improve the value of the materials available to you and to customize and improve the content and/or layout of our pages based on visitor interest.
Information You Provide
If you submit your personal information to LSB online, we use this information for such purposes as to responding to your request, providing requested information about our product and service offerings and communicating with you. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, phone number and e-mail address.
Cookies
Like most websites, a technology called cookies may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. We do not use cookies to gather personal information such as a person’s name or email address. We gather this type of information so that we can refine and personalize the content that you and other visitors will see on our website.
Links to Other Sites
LSB's website may contain links to other sites such as LSB subsidiaries, distributors and sales affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Changes to this Statement
LSB may occasionally update this privacy statement without prior notice to reflect changes in our online information practices. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. We encourage you to refer to this statement from time to time for updates to the statement.
Footer Menu
Contact Us Legal / Terms of UsePrivacy Statement
© 2019 LSB Industries. All Rights Reserved.
